"大杀器" 拿点"大杀器"过来
WMD. Got that WMD here.
我要的是你们上次那种
I'm looking for what you had the other day.
不就这个吗
This shit right here?
上次你们是叫它"本拉登"
The other day you was calling it bin Laden.
现在叫"大杀器"(WMD)了
But now it's WMD.
它会让你爽翻天
It will mass destruct your ass.
这是上等货?
So this the hi-test?
新瓶装旧酒
Same shit, new name.
包你满意
You be all right.
好了 穿好衣服
Okay, get dressed.
我给你熨了衣服放在楼上
I pressed you some clothes and laid them out upstairs.
还有别忘了书包
And don't forget that book bag neither.
家伙带了吗 小子?
You got your chrome, young one?
我的枪给我
I'll take mine.
注意交叉火力 都听见了没?
Y'all mind the crossfire, you hear?
出发
Let's go.
他们冲巷子来了
They coming up the alley! They coming up the alley!
他们回来了
They coming back!
瞄准胸口 兄弟 懂了吗
Aim for the chest, brother, you hear me?
让开
Slide up.
趴在地上别动 听见了吗
You get down on that floor and stay there, you hear?
- 听见了吗 儿子? - 好的 妈妈
- You hear me, boy? - Okay, Mama.
上 上
Come on! Come on!
靠
Fuck!
- 你跑什么 - 妈的
- Why you running? - What the fuck?
该死
Oh, shit!
毙了那黑鬼
Hit that nigger cold.
贱人
Bitches!
你躲什么
Why you hiding?
枪战结束了 孩子
Drama done with, boy.
拿上书包上学去
You gotta get your bags and get yourself to school.
上车 该死 上车
Get in, damn it! Get in.
T.T. 听见了吗
T.T., you hear me?
下来吧 枪战结束了
Come on now. The drama's done.
拿上书包上学去
Get your bags and get yourself to school.
我说了 快准备好...
I told you, you gotta get ready...
不!
No!
火线重案组 第二季 第九集  偏离目标
The Wire S02E09 Stray Rounds
* When you walk through the garden *
* You gotta watch your back *
* Well I beg your pardon *
* Walk the straight and narrow track *
* If you walk with Jesus *
* He's gonna save your soul *
* You gotta keep the devil *
* Way down in the hole *
* He's got the fire and the fury *
* At his command *
* Well you don't have to worry *
* If you hold on to Jesus hand *
* We'll all be safe from Satan *
* When the thunder rolls *
* Just gotta help me keep the devil *
* Way down in the hole *
* You gotta help me keep the devil *
"世界是越来越小了"  ---"希腊人"
他们模式变了?
They're changing up?
我要问问我订的按摩沙发 你手头有我的五个吧?
Looking for my La-Z-Boys. Five of them you got for me, right?
- 明天发货 - 知道了
- That shipment is tomorrow. - Got it.
这还是几天前 我们从Newkirk的仓库听到的
That's what the Newkirk warehouse was giving us a few days back.
开门见山要毒品 一点都不拐弯抹角
Straight, to-the-point drug talk. No muss, no fuss.
现在你听
Now listen.
金字塔公司 有什么能效劳的?
Pyramid, Inc. May I help you?
你们有Davinas组合沙发之类的吗
You got them Davinas or what?
据我了解 我们已经不再提供此类品种了 先生
I'm told we no longer carry that line, sir.
我 Kima Herc和Carver...
Between me, Kima, Herc and Carver...
自从我们从码头跟踪卡车 到了那个仓库...
we been sitting on that warehouse every minute...
就一直监视着它
since we followed that truck off the docks.
没有毒贩出入
No players coming in or going out.
也没有涉毒的交易运输
No drug-related traffic at all.
最糟糕的是 从那以后 Sobotka再也没用过手机
To top it off, Sobotka hasn't used his cell phone since.
- 我们哪里露了马脚 - 也许是第二个集装箱
- We tipped our hand somewhere. - That second can, maybe.
码头警察拦下他们 肯定引起了他们的警觉
The port police making a traffic stop on their cargo must've spooked them.
如果是那样 我们就弄巧成拙了
If that's what did it, we fucked ourselves over nothing.
他们把那集装箱当做送错的 给丢弃了
They dumped that can as a misdelivery.
- 什么? - 可能他们偷梁换柱了
- What? - They probably changed that up, too.
如果他们认为我们在查他们...
If they think we're onto them...
他们会调换箱子以防万一
they switch the can themselves, just to be safe.
里面装点垃圾运出码头...
And it goes off the docks with some bullshit inside...
看看我们会不会拦下他们
just to see if we pull them up.
而我们确实这么做了
Which we did.
我做了
Which I did.
不 他们还没有完全发现我们
No, they're not on us completely.
如果有 他们早就关了仓库 逃跑了
If they were, they'd be shutting that warehouse down and rolling out.
他们只是
Instead, they're just
等在那地方 回绝生意...
sitting inside that place, turning away calls...
等着我们放弃
waiting us out.
我可是个很有耐心的货
I, for one, am a patient motherfucker.
别浪费胶卷
Don't waste film.
我在这待太久了
I been here so fucking long
看你都觉得顺眼了
that you're starting to look good to me.
有情况吗?
Anything?
进去的毒品总该出来 不是吗? 我是说 他妈的怎么回事
The drugs go in, they gotta come out, right? I mean, what the fuck?
晚了点
Little late.
过去一个9岁儿童路上跌倒...
used to be When a 9-year-old kid hit the pavement...
区警长几分钟就到现场了
a district commander would be there within minutes.
我猜我们活在一个美好新世界里
I guess we're living in a brave new world.
接到报告时我跟Burrell正在华盛顿
I was in Washington with Burrell when I heard.
在特区? 为什么
D. C? What for?
Burrell带了几个区的头儿一起去司法部...
Burrell took some district commanders down to DOJ with him...
为一些蝇头小利努力卖笑
pimping ourselves for a little grant money.
什么情况
So what do we got?
一个9岁小孩在他卧室里...
Nine-year-old in his bedroom...
被颗长眼的流弹误中
catches a seeing-eye stray through the window.
- 死了? - 已经在医院宣布死亡
- Dead? - Pronounced at University.
- 证人呢 - 没人出来指证...
- Witnesses? - No one offering a name...
大体上是两个黑帮的地盘之争
but the general theme is two crews arguing over the real estate.
地上发现了至少三种不同口径的子弹
We got casings from at least three different calibers on the ground.
我们会彻查 但你的人和机动部队...
We're gonna canvass hard, but your people and Tactical...
应该捣毁贩毒点 实施逮捕
should hit the area drug corners and collect bodies.
整一个乱枪打鸟
Fucking pointless.
抓到够多的鸟人 案子自然就破了
We jack up enough shitbirds, this case can fall.
我不是说那个 我知道那套
I ain't talking about that. I know the drill.
我是说这整件破事
I'm talking about this whole mess.
不过是从一头赶到另一头 却把这当成了对策
Been chasing this shit from one corner to the next like it's a plan.
去端点吧 Howard 搞点成绩
Hit the corners, Howard. Take scalps.
能让你觉得好过点
You'll feel better when you do.
你告诉过我们世通改名的故事 不是吗?
You told us about WorldCom and the name change-up, right?
- 你说... - 我说改货的名字
- You said that... - I said change the name of our product.
没说把人赶出地盘
I didn't say nothing about taking people off a corner.
听着 我们已经给那些垃圾货 改了太多次名字了...
look, We done changed the name of that weak shit so many times...
没人再来高楼区买了
that don't nobody come down to the Towers no more.
而那些Carrollton来的人 还冒出来抢生意
And them Carrollton boys had it going on.
谁开枪打了那孩子
Who shot the young one?
不知道 我想不是我们的人
I don't know. I don't think it was us.
他们那帮黑鬼都疯了 我是说...
Them other niggers was going wild, though, I mean...
你知道 警察...
You know, the cops...
这次要杀鸡儆猴了
are gonna have to bang some heads on this one.
肯定的
They got to.
这意味着风声过去前 我们都得关门大吉
That means we gotta shut everything down until this shit pass.
高楼区 平房区
That means the Towers, the low-rises.
所有生意都得歇上很长时间!
Everything gotta take a long fucking time-out!
我知道 String
I know, String.
抱歉 伙计
I'm sorry, man.
我告诉你 伙计
Let me tell you something, man.
这游戏
This here game,
不只是看你的名声...
it's more than the rep you carry...
你的地盘
the corner you hold.
该硬的时候是得硬 我知道
You gotta be fierce, I know that.
但更多时候
But more than that,
你得能屈能伸
you gotta show some flex.
一手大棒一手胡萝卜
Give and take on both sides.
- 听懂了吗 - 懂了
- You hear me? - Yeah.
好了 每一把街头枪战里的枪...
All right, anything that fired a bullet out on that corner...
都得消失 明白吗
has gotta disappear, you understand me?
我可不是说扔进下水道
I'm not talking about the storm drains.
联系Shamrock  让他开车 把所有枪都扔进海里
Call that nigger Shamrock and drive all that chrome over to the harbor.
好的
All right.
到了
Coming up.
有人还在等着我的货...
I got people waiting on a package from me...
但Sergei说在我们确定那群警察之前...
but Sergei says that until we're sure about the police...
会有几天不做那买卖
We're not going to be doing that business for a few days.
你叔叔小心谨慎是对的
Your uncle, he is right to be careful.
但Niko...
But, Niko...
如果你想做这买卖
if you are going to be doing this,
你不该找我们谈
you should not be talking to us about it.
为什么
Why not?
我们更像 你们怎么说来着
We are more, what you call,
批发商
wholesalers.
我只算个小散户 是吗?
I'm kind of small-time, huh?
你算不上大户
You are not so big, but
但你是我们的朋友
you're among friends.
打这个电话
Call that number.
跟他谈
Talk to him.
Mike?
"麦克白"?
This White Mike?
你认识他?
You know him?
在Curtis湾就认识
From Curtis Bay.
我跟他一起上南区高中
I went to Southern High School with the guy.
你跟我们是一伙的...
You are with us now, so...
他不会为难你的 没事
he will be fair. No problem.
现在
Now,
我们的另一桩买卖...
for the rest of our business...
我们要让这些集装箱消失
We will disappear these containers.
都是合法的
All of them clean.
送到Newkirk街
Take them to Newkirk Street.
如果有问题 他们会拦下卡车...
If there is a problem, they will stop the trucks...
或者我们会见到警察
or we will see the police.
如果没有
If not,
就无须担心了
no more worries.
好的
All right.
仓库的电话停了吧?
We are off the warehouse phone now?
昨天一天我都在给我们的人交代新号码
All day yesterday, I was giving the new number to our people.
真操蛋
This is bullshit.
如果他们盯上了卡车 那他们...
If they were onto the truck, then they...
他们早就上去搜了 不是吗
they would've searched it, no?
条子来了!
Five-O!
你们要去哪
Where you guys going?
过来 你们知道怎么回事
Come on, you know the deal.
靠墙站好 快
Get the fuck up against the wall! Hurry up!
快 动起来
Come on, keep moving.
抓到了 趴下
Get him. Down. down. down
扯淡 你知道我什么都没干
This is bullshit, man. You know I ain't did nothing, man.
每个到中央登记处的可领取
Everybody gets the special downtown at central booking:
一块香肠三明治和一杯牛奶
One baloney sandwich and one white milk.
- 闭上鸟嘴 - 伙计 我是清白的 听见没
- Just shut the fuck up. - Man, I'm clean, you hear me?
那你来平房区干嘛?
What are you doing in the Pit then?
向毒品说不
Saying no to drugs.
别只是向毒品说不啊
Don't just say no to drugs, motherfucker.
得说 "不了 谢谢"
Say,"No, thank you."
把头低下 上车
Put your fucking head down, step up and get in.
坐这 蠢货 进去时小心头
Sit down right here, stupid. Watch your head going in.
坐过去 混蛋
Slide over, asshole.
等孩子被杀了才这么干 真是惭愧啊
Shame a kid had to get killed before we got around to doing this.
我们这算是在干什么
What exactly is it that we're doing?
小孩子被流弹杀了
Young boy killed over bullshit.
现在警察追着你的屁股不放
Now you got the police crawling all the way up your ass.
我得说 能在东区真好
It's a good day to be an Eastside nigger, I gotta say.
事实上 如果我接受你的提议
Thing is, it ain't gonna happen like that
事情就不会变成这样了
if I take you up on your offer.
我会有好货卖
I'll be out there selling that real.
我手下也不会斗殴
My boys ain't gonna be scuffling.
没有斗殴 也就不会在街头搞火拼 挑起这一切
They ain't gonna be scuffling or standing on nobody's else's corner, starting no shit.
你是西区的
You're Westside.
一定听说过Charlie Sollers 对吧?
You must've heard of Charlie Sollers, right?
没有
No.
那是Franklin和Fremont时代
Goes all the way back to Franklin and Fremont.
我是说 得追溯到60年代
I mean, all the way back to the '60s and shit.
- Sollers? - 卖海洛因像卖水一样
- Sollers? - Sold heroin like it was water.
我是说 那混球挣了好些钱
I mean, the motherfucker made himself some money.
我不知道你他妈说的是谁
I don't know who the fuck you talking about.
我知道你不知道
I know you don't.
警察也不知道
And the police don't.
那些小强盗更不知道
And the stick-up boys wouldn't have a fucking clue either.
因为Charlie Sollers只贩毒
'Cause Charlie Sollers just sold dope.
没有案底 籍籍无名
No profile, no street rep.
只是低买高卖
Just buy for $1, sell for $2.
有时你们无路可退了
Sometimes, when your back up against the wall,
就会诉诸武力
you go to the gun.
我了解 我过去也那样
I know. I been there.
但你们不能靠武力过活
But you ain't gotta live by it.
Avon...
Avon是个斗士
Avon's a soldier.
打拼的时候你会想靠他
That's who you want with you when the shit fly.
但做生意...
But as far as business go...
你还有门路?
You still got that connect?
刚下的船 String
Right off the boat, String.
好吧
All right.
我用你的进价买入...
I'm gonna buy from you at the price you paying...
同时我让你们进驻高层区
and I'll let you walk that shit straight in the Towers.
我给你们734号
You can have 734,
770号和221号
770 and 221.
我留着其他三栋
I keep the other three.
你怎么跟Avon说
How you gonna tell it to Avon?
明智之举 不是吗
It makes sense, don't it?
有道理他自然会听
He gonna hear something when it makes sense.
对吧
Right?
不赖吧
No shit.
还以为你跟Nicky一块呢
I thought you was in with Nicky.
去他的Nick
Fuck Nick.
他说你是"他的另一半"
He said you was his other half.
我才不要他臭钱
I don't want his fucking money.
我是说 那是毒品钱
I mean, that's drug money.
毒品不是好东西
And fucking drugs are bad, right?
你得考虑那东西对社区的危害
I mean, you gotta consider what that shit does to the community.
Ziggy 这几年你都在跟着"麦克白"混 难道你忘记了?
You spent all last year fucking around with White Mike. You remember that?
人会长大的
A man can grow.
再说
Besides,
我脑子里构思的这买卖 能让它们都黯然失色
I got a caper in mind that is gonna put that horseshit to shame.
我实话跟你说吧
i mean, I'm telling you.
你要入伙吗
You want in?
我需要做什么
What do I gotta do?
露一手码头工人的绝活 Johnny
What a longshoreman does best, Johnny.
Zig 你的鸭子不会喝派克斯维尔黑麦吧
Zig, your duck won't touch the Pikesville rye?
酒吧里酒架上的酒按档次由高向下排列
他喝中档酒 不喝低档货
He drinks mid-shelf. He don't like that rail shit.
我丢了右腿还换不来...
Fuck if I wouldn't give my right leg
一杯酒 就扯淡了
for a shot and a beer.
New Charles来了
New Charles in the house.
- 走起来还不错 - 准备装个假肢
- Moving pretty good. - Waiting on a prosthetic.
找了个像样的律师?
You got a decent lawyer?
Nat Coxson通过工会帮我牵的线
oh, Nat Coxson hooked me up through the union.
鸭子是带谁来的?
What's with the duck?
- Ziggy - Charlie
看样子你该改名字了
thing is you know you gotta let go of your name.
- 什么 - 对
- Say what? - Yeah,
一条腿的小丑不配叫New Charles
New Charles don't work no more for a one-legged fuck.
对 也许该叫"义肢"
Yeah, maybe "Stump."
知道吗 "假腿"
You know what? "Peg."
"新假腿仔"
"New Peggy."
- 叫"歪哥"怎么样 - 歪哥?
- How about "Tilt"? - Tilt?
歪哥 就像弹球机(弹球机台面是倾斜的)
Tilt. Just like a pinball machine.
歪哥 我喜欢
Tilt. I like that.
对 我几天前打过一次
uh, Yeah, I called a couple of nights ago.
我说过今晚会进城 记得吗
Told you I might be in town tonight, remember?
这么说这是你第一次?
So, this is your first time?
对 第一次
Yep, first time for me.
你干哪行的 Jimmy?
What do you do, Jimmy?
警察吗
Are you the police?
- 为警察办事? - 不 上帝 不
- Do you work with the police? - No. Christ, no.
我是跑单的推销员
No, I'm a traveling salesman.
我到处跑 你知道...
I travel and, you know...
你住哪
Where do you live?
不告诉你
I'm not gonna tell you that.
我住在城外
I live out of town.
抱歉 我们今晚不能给你提供服务
I'm sorry. I don't think we can help you tonight.
谢谢
Thank you.
你太逊了
You sucked.
真的很逊
I mean, really.
我怎么知道会要被问东问西?
Fuck if I thought I was gonna be interrogated.
我是说 老天 我不过是个 寻求安慰的寂寞男人不是吗
I mean, Christ, I'm just a guy looking to get laid, right?
嘿 傻帽
Hey, fucknuts.
你他妈怎么回事
What the fuck is wrong with you?
靠 Ziggy
Christ, Ziggy.
老天 Zig 搞什么
Jesus, Zig. What the fuck?
我表弟怎么了
What's up with my cousin?
别跟我提那混蛋
Don't even talk to me about that asshole.
- 把自己给喝死了 - 该死
- Drank himself to death. - Oh, shit.
不过 哪个白痴会给鸭子喝威士忌啊
What kind of fool would give a duck whiskey anyhow?
那小子是不正常
That boy ain't right.
他的傻鸟根本没酒量
And his fucking bird couldn't hold liquor for shit.
La-Z-Boys(按摩沙发的牌子)
La-Z-Boys?
还有Davinas(组合沙发的牌子)
And Davinas.
"男"和"女"
Male and female.
- 麻药和可卡因 - "Davina"是什么
- Dope and coke. - What the hell is a Davina?
类似某种双人沙发
It's like a love seat, kind of.
- 有说重量单位吗 - 都是整数
- Any line on weight? - All whole numbers.
没有一半 四分之一 八分之一?
No halves, quarters, eight-balls?
盎司?
Ounces?
家具的数目他们都提到过几种?
What kind of numbers they putting on the furniture?
不超过五
Nothing much above five.
"建议乔"占着Ashland以北的地盘
Proposition Joe has Ashland all the way up to North.
至少十个街角
Ten corners, easy.
五盎司还不够塞牙缝的
Five ounces wouldn't last him past lunch.
是公斤
It's kilos.
我们发现大东家了
We're on the main stem.
昨晚有什么进出
so What was coming and going last night?
没多少
Not much.
没有卡车 只有小轿车进出...
No trucks in, some cars in and out...
但我们之前看到的毒贩都没了影
but none of the drug players we saw rolling up there before.
不管上次那一卡车运的是什么
Whatever was in that last truckload
大概都用汽车行李箱运出去了
probably went out in car trunks.
他们现在正在哪分销呢
They're doing their distribution somewhere else for now.
正因此我们头号工作是 找到一个有用的电话
Which is why job one is to get back to a good phone.
只要和对仓库电话采取行动的 成立依据一样
The same PC that got you on that warehouse phone...
你们就可以监听到其他任意电话
will get you anywhere else you want to go.
我们只需要知道他们的新号码
All we need is the new number.
最近Verizon电话公司 有在那接入新线吗?
Verizon running any new lines in there lately?
我们跟电信安全部门的人联系过 他们说没有
We talked to the phone security people. They say no.
可能改用手机了
Probably going to a cell phone.
最好能从俄国佬的手机上获得新号码
Best bet is to get the new number off the Russian's cell phone.
好的 就这样
Okay, then.
Freamon和Prez 在窃听室值第一班
Freamon and Prez, stay on one shift in the wiretap room.
Bunk和Russell 第二班
Bunk and Russell, man the other.
Herc和Carver
Herc and Carver,
继续监视Newkirk街
you guys are on Newkirk Street waiting to see
看看仓库的走私活动是否恢复
if the warehouse traffic picks back up.
McNulty和Greggs继续追查卖淫集团
McNulty and Greggs have a line into the prostitution ring.
但目前为止 幕后操纵姑娘的人...
But so far, the people handling the girls...
对招待新嫖客相当谨慎
have been a little cautious about fresh johns.
所以我们得换个角度
So we're gonna need a new angle there.
有问题吗
Questions?
你们怎么跟那些女孩说的
What was your play with those girls?
郊外的推销员
Out-of-town salesman.
郊外多远?
How far out of town?
什么意思
What do you mean?
离城越远她们越容易相信
The farther out of town, the more they believe.
越不觉得你听上去像警察
Less like a cop you sound.
你会学些口音吗
You do any accents?
英格兰 不列颠 苏格兰之类的口音?
English, British, Scottish, something like that?
我勒个去!
Crikey!
当我远渡重洋来到这儿...
I was looking to get a little hanky-panky...
想找点小乐子 这家伙...
and this one bloke gave me this number to call
就给了我这号码让我打
when I got across the pond.
就这么办 小子 就这么办
Work on it, son. work on it.
20万?
$200,000?
还不到他们欠的四分之一
That isn't a quarter of what they owe.
他们说货物通关后
They say they will pay another $200,000
会再付20万
once their shipment clears the docks.
然后呢
And then?
没了
That is all.
这些哥伦比亚人没信义 Spiros
These Colombians are without honor, Spiros.
都是骗子
They are cheats.
我们送过去的化学品都很好 不是吗
The chemicals we sent are good, no?
没什么可抱怨的
No complaint.
他们甚至说要更多
They say they want more, even.
而他们也清楚
And they understand that
我们能保证他们的货通关?
we can guarantee their product gonna clear Customs?
对
Right.
但他们还想贪小便宜
And still, they try to chisel.
为什么
Why?
他们怎么想的
What are they thinking?
他们觉得我们一本万利
That it is all profit for us.
就算只出原价的一半 我们也会接受
That we will settle for half of what we agreed...
因为四十万也是一笔大钱了
because $400,000 is still a lot of money.
"希腊人"会生气的
The Greek will be angry.
这就是生意 Eton
This is business, Eton.
"希腊人"?
The Greek?
他会见招拆招
He will be smart.
上帝
Jesus.
意外地枪杀了一个在卧室里的9岁小孩...
You accidentally shoot one 9-year-old in his bedroom...
就闹得满城风雨了
and the whole city gets its undies in a bunch.
我常说 人有失蹄
To err is human, that's what I like to say.
市长为上镜昨晚去了现场
The mayor went to the scene for the cameras last night.
还说不会再放任犯罪了
Said the crime will not stand.
嗯 我们告诉市长 我们还没找到目击证人
yeah, we tell the mayor we're still working without an eyeball witness.
有没有小道消息
How about the street talk?
有人提到一个17岁 诨名Bodie的家伙
I got some mentions of a 17-year-old with the streetname Bodie.
在缉毒科有案底 叫Preston Broadus
Narcotics has him as Preston Broadus.
那为啥小Preston没被带到审讯室里
And why is young Preston not being hurled with great abandon
听着我们的人鬼吼呢
around one of our interrogation rooms?
我们说话这会儿 已派车到他祖母家了
We got cars on his grandma's as we speak.
你他妈以为你在跟谁说话 外行吗?
What the fuck you think you're dealing with here? Amateurs?
去他的Nick 这是我的生意
Fuck Nick. This is my thing.
你想干 就得跟我谈
You want in, you gotta deal with me.
好了 我有S级和SL级的奔驰
All right, I got S-Class and SL-Class Benzes.
跑车 轿车 篷车
Roadsters, sedans, cabriolets.
全新的 钥匙还在点火装置上
I got them brand new, with the keys in the ignition.
完好无缺
Nothing stripped.
码头外?
Off the docks?
当然在码头外
No shit, off the docks.
你看我长得像卖车的吗
What the fuck do I look like, a fucking car dealer?
我抽两成 但是...
Twenty on the dollar. but...
如果我们合作
if we're gonna do this,
你至少得收三辆
I'm gonna need you to order a minimum of three.
否则不值得我冒险
Or else it ain't worth it for me.
S430的基本价七万三
Now, base price on an S430 starts at $73,000.
你卖掉...
You round it, I get...
我每辆收一万五
$15,000 for each car that you want.
傻子
Malaka
赃车就是赃车
A stolen car is a stolen car.
没有拥车证(汽车的所有权证明书) 哪怕是开一万块去 有谁会买?
Without title, who is going to pay even $10,000 for it?
当然 也许在Baltimore是这样
Sure, in Baltimore, maybe.
但在你家乡...
But where you're from...
我打赌 很多都不介意...
I'll bet you got family that don't give two fucks...
一辆美国车是带不带"拥车证"
whether or not an American car got a title on it.
如果一个你这样的国际企业家
Man, it would be a sad state of affairs...
连几辆额外的奔驰车都不敢接
if an international entrepreneur such as yourself...
还真够悲剧的
didn't know what to do with a couple of extra Mercedes.
Jimmy McNulty的大喜之夜啊
Big night for Jimmy McNulty.
或者该说James Cromwell 来自Knightsbridge
Or should I say James Cromwell of Knightsbridge
Stepney&Mersey
Stepney and Mersey.
你说什么
Excuse me?
Cromwell领导了英国资产阶级革命
Cromwell是个窃取我先祖土地的混账
Cromwell was the English fuck who stole my ancestors' land
其他都是从摇滚歌曲里来的(出自"Play with Fire")
and the other ones are all from rock 'n' roll songs.
总之 明晚十点...
Anyways, 10:00 tomorrow night...
在Russell街的停车场有车来接我
the shuttle comes for me on the parking lot off Russell Street.
干得好
Good work.
让Greggs给你装好监听设备 并准备好监视车
We'll get Greggs to wire you up and set the surveillance.
遗憾的是我们还没搞到一个有用的电话
Shame we're not up on a good phone right now.
要是在抄妓院时能惊动监听那头 会很有收获
Be nice to tickle the wire when we raid the brothel.
运气好的话
A little luck,
也许我们能在那有所准备
maybe we get back up before then.
还有件事
One other thing.
我很疑惑一个涉案如此深的俄国人...
I'm bothered that a Russian immigrant this deep in dirt...
在执法机关居然没有案底
doesn't have anything in a law enforcement computer.
你跟Woodlawn的朋友还有联系吗(FBI在该地的分支)
You still got that friend over in Woodlawn?
我想知道FBI的数据库有没有记录
I'd like to know what the FBI has in its database.
在讨论Barksdale案不欢而散后...
well, After that meeting on the Barksdale case...
我有点把他惹毛了 记得吗
I made a point of pissing him off, remember?
那又怎样 你把人都得罪光了
So what? You do that to everybody.
他是George Glekas
This is George Glekas.
第二个集装箱被运至的...
He's the cat who owns the appliance store
电器行店主
where that second can landed.
也把他查一下
Run his ass, too.
为什么不找个人入伙 把它们开出Bobtail道
Why not just cut another guy in and run them out the bobtail lane?
这些小宝贝一消失
These babies start disappearing
中转站里所有人都会怀疑是内鬼
and everybody on the terminal is gonna suspect an inside job.
我们需要断线钳剪开铁丝网...
We're gonna need bolt cutters for the fence...
接着还需要足够的木梁...
and then we're gonna need enough wood beams...
搭个跨过草坪通到公路的小道
to make a track across the grass onto the road.
那么麻烦干嘛 我们能直接把车
Why bother? We can run them cars
开过那些小草坪 没问题
over that little patch of grass, no problem.
那不是计划
That ain't the plan.
我刚看到一个集装箱消失了
I just saw a can disappear.
- Talco公司? - Pakusa卸的货?
- Talco line? - Pakusa working it?
是他 我们要跟踪吗
It's him. Do we try to follow?
我们知道要送到哪 对吗
We know where it's going, right?
12-08 收到吗
12-08, you copy?
12-08收到 怎么了
12-08, what's up?
有个集装箱可能离开码头 去你们那儿
We got a can that might be coming to you off the port.
集装箱号 PMQV...
Can number: Paul-Mike-Quebec-Victor...
4-0-0-7-6-5
4-0-0-7-6-5,
校验码2
check digit two.
我们要做什么
What do you want us to do with it?
看它是否被送达
See if it arrives.
如果送达了呢
And if it does?
看看接下来发生什么
See what happens then.
有件事你想知道吗 Carv?
You wanna know something, Carv?
我开始觉得作为犯罪调查人员...
I'm starting to think that as criminal investigators...
我们没有得到真正的尊重
we're not really respected.
没必要 Jimmy
That ain't necessary, Jimmy.
我知道我们在Barksdale案上 浪费了彼此时间
I knew we were fucking the dog on that Barksdale thing.
我能找谁说
Who do I tell?
我们的新助理特别主管 只在乎忠诚和拍马屁
We got this new ASAC, thinks it's all about loyalty and ass-kiss.
相信我 这里跟你们局不一样
And believe me, this ain't like your agency.
你惹恼上面 他们让你去开船
You piss them off, you ride the boat.
在这...
Here...well,
你会在某天清早来上班时 发现自己被派到...
you come into work one morning, you find yourself assigned to some
Arkansas某个干旱的印第安保留地了
fucking dustbowl Indian res in Arkansas.
- 总之 我是说得过分了 Fitz - 管他呢
- Still, I was out of line, Fitz. - Fuck it.
你那是什么 哥们?
What you got there, brother?
白人 不一样了嘛
White boys. A different look for you.
有趣的是 他们都没案底
Funny thing is, they're all showing clean.
可能性有多大
What's the chance of that?
总之 NCIC(国家犯罪信息中心)和NADDIS(危险麻醉药品信息库)都没记录
Anyways, NCIC and NADDIS are a dead end.
海关有点这家伙的情报 叫Glekas
Customs had a little intel on this guy, Glekas.
你说海关有他的情报?
You said Customs had intel on him?
那该有显示
Should show here.
搜索完毕 没有结果
我试试别的方式
Let me try something else with it.
这能提供我们整个调查局 范围内关于你目标的情报
This'll give us any contact your boy might have had with us, agency-wide.
办案特工:Ernest Koutris 编号:2379 办公室:圣地亚哥
圣地亚哥那边有线索
Got something out of San Diego.
- Glekas的? - 看看吧
- On Glekas? - We'll see.
天呐 要是我给Hyattsville打个长途...
geez, I make a long distance call to Hyattsville...
就得填三份表 还要警督批准
I need three forms and a lieutenant's approval.
你好 请接Ernest Koutris探员
Yes, Agent Ernest Koutris, please.
相信我 我们这的文书工作也不少
Believe me, we ain't short on paperwork here either.
Koutris探员?
Agent Koutris?
不多
Not much to it.
我们在我95 96年办的一件 失窃物品案中逮了他
We pulled his chain in a stolen goods case I worked in '95, '96.
他只是个小角色 就没起诉 但我进行了审问
He was just crumbs, so no charges. But I did an interview.
我觉得这家伙只是在投机倒把
The guy struck me as just a mope playing it slick.
嗯 你想要我可以把资料发给你
Yeah, if you want, I can send you what I got.
好的
All right.
你需要就找我吧
If you need it, let me know.
我们得谈谈
We need to talk.
有人跟踪吗
Anyone following?
没有
no
到街上走走
Run up and down the street.
把车牌号记下
Take tag numbers from cars.
- 我这个干了一周 没有发现啊 - 再干一次
- All week I've done it. Nothing. - Again.
卡车来了
The truck is here.
Lester 卡车来了
Lester, it's here.
他们卸了什么吗
They offload anything?
还没有
Not yet.
好的 等着
Okay, wait on it.
你看 现在情况是 Preston
See, the thing about it, Preston,
你蠢得不可思议
is that you're unbelievably stupid.
真的
You are.
我不是想打击你 只是说出实情
I don't say it to upset you. Just to state a fact.
他不这么想
He doesn't think so.
没人会觉得自己蠢 这也是蠢的一种
Nobody ever thinks they're stupid. It's part of the stupidity.
不用你告诉我们那个街角发生了什么
we don't even need you to tell us what happened on that corner.
我们都知道
We know what happened.
我们抓到了你 找到了枪 整个经过都清楚了
We got you, we got your guns, we got the whole fucking story.
我的律师在哪 伙计
Where that lawyer at, man?
看见没 你搞砸了
See, you just fucked up.
看你看着这包的样子
Way you looked at the bag,
你知道里面是什么 不是吗
you know what's in there, don't you?
正是你
That's you, right there,
搞砸了这些
fucking up.
- 我不知道你在说什么 - 不 你搞砸了
- I don't know what you talking about. - No, you fucked up.
我们甚至在枪上找到了你的指纹
We even got your prints on one of the guns. We even got that.
哪把?
Which one?
就是这把
That's you right there.
律师
Lawyer.
他们问起我?
They were asking about me?
圣地亚哥
San Diego.
圣地亚哥是陈年旧事了
San Diego was a long time ago.
我们华盛顿的朋友不知道他们为什么问
Our friend in Washington does not know why.
总之他们是问了
Only that the people asked.
你跟我说查那些女尸的警察是当地的
You told me the police looking into the women were local.
没错
They were.
没有FBI参与
No FBI.
我们已经运送过合法的集装箱了吗
We've been running only clean containers?
是的 没人监视 也没人跟踪
Yes. And no one watches, no one follows.
没人拦车
No one stops anything.
货仓的电话也换过了?
And we changed the warehouse phone?
那再过一两天
A day or two more,
我们又可以开门营业了
and we are back to business.
我们观察 步步谨慎  但可以开门营业了
We watch, we are careful. But we are back to business.
你该帮帮我们的朋友不是吗
You will have to do a favor for our friend, no?
要公平
Fair is fair.
哥伦比亚人 我想
The Colombians, I think.
他们拿走我们的化学品 却不按承诺付款
They take our chemicals and pay less than promised.
在家乡 我了解到人人都是恐怖分子
Down there, I understand everyone is a terrorist now.
法官被杀 街头炸弹 很糟糕
Judges are killed. Bombs go off in the street. It's very bad.
那些骗我们的哥伦比亚人
The Colombians who cheated us,
他们可不是游击队的
they're not with the guerrillas.
只是些垃圾
They're trash.
世界是越来越小了
The world is a smaller place now.
而FBI对这些事
And the FBI cares very much
很关注
about such things.
要公平
Fair is fair.
Sergei正在打电话
Sergei's making a call.
如无意外 就送"按摩沙发"来
If there is no problem, then bring in the La-Z-Boys.
我们在那见
I will meet you there.
听得出这声音吗
Recognize that voice?
货仓接电话的那个 对吗
That's the man from the warehouse phone, right?
- 是同一个人? - 同一个人 新号码
- That's the same guy? - Same guy, new number.
你打给谁
Who you calling?
Pearlman 她在家
Pearlman, at home.
再准备一份宣誓书  我们就能查回这东家了
Another affidavit, and we're back on the main stem.
这货是纯的 String
Shit is raw, String.
我是说 能在里面掺东西
I mean, you can stomp on this motherfucker.
好的
All right.
那么 等警察不在高楼区大开杀戒了
So, when them police stop busting heads up in them Towers...
你们就让Prop Joe的人接手其中三栋
you all let Prop Joe's people take hold of three of them.
好的
All right.
好了 把电话记录加进模板文件里就搞定了
Okay, add the DNR stuff to the boilerplate, and you're there.
把每个点联起来...
Start connecting the dots...
你不得不想 这些家伙还有什么不干的
and you have to start asking yourself what these guys aren't into.
毒品 女人 赃物 五毒俱全
Drugs, women, stolen goods. All of them.
FBI没什么消息
FBI didn't have much.
只查到点Glekas在圣地亚哥犯的事...
A little something out of San Diego on Glekas...
一个已结案的失窃物品案
in a stolen goods case that was closed out.
圣地亚哥?
San Diego?
这些家伙还流窜作案
These guys move around.
- 拿那衣服干嘛 - 约会之夜
- What's with the suit? - Date night.
妓院的卧底任务
The undercover at the brothel.
赶紧的 女士
Run like hell, ma'am.
我们想尽快窃听电话  这样就能听到今晚突击行动后他们的反应
We wanna be up on that phone, so we hear what we hear after tonight's raid.
宣誓者是谁
Who's the affiant?
你能偷到海蓝色的SL系列吗
Can you get the SL-series in Pacific blue?
那就最好了
That would be best.
你要什么都行 老大
Whatever you need, chief.
这款的颜色我不关心
I don't give a damn about the color of this one.
什么颜色都行
Whatever you have.
不成问题 它们都有活动天窗
Ain't a problem. They all just gotta have sunroofs.
一言难尽
It's a long story.
下周二是个好日子
Next Tuesday would be good for us.
周三早上有艘船 因此...
A ship comes Wednesday early, so...
听着...
Listen...
我能要些预付款吗
you think I can get an advance on this?
我现在有些开销 但手头有点紧
I got some expenses right now, and I'm a little tapped.
- 我就问问 - 货到付款
- I'm just asking. - Payment on delivery.
嘿 不用担心 老大
hey, Don't worry about it, chief.
骗你这种精明的生意人 我想都不敢想
I would never even dream of cheating a smart businessman like yourself.
光是我一个人操心这些还不够
It ain't enough that I gotta be the one thinking this whole shit through.
光是我一个人小心这个 小心那个还不够
That I gotta be the one looking out for this shit and that shit.
检查这个 确保那事搞定
Checking up on this, making sure this shit is done.
不 不够
No, that's not enough.
正因此那些操蛋的CEO能赚那么多
That's why they be paying them fucking CEOs so much damn money.
因为当事情搞砸了
Because when the shit fall bad,
都是他们承担责任
it all fall bad on them.
其他人可以做缩头乌龟 想干什么干什么
Everybody else can be ducking and hiding, doing what they fucking wanna do.
但事到临头...
But when push come to shove...
是我承担责任...
I'm the one who's got to take that responsibility...
而你们全部给我帮倒忙
and y'all are leaving me very little to work with right now.
- 等等 String... - 不 这是件很简单的事 小的们
- Hold up, String... - No, that's a very simple thing, my nigger.
很简单
very simple
你们开车把枪带到水边
You drive the guns to the water.
看看四周
You look around,
看见四下无人
you ain't see anybody,
就把枪扔了
you throw the guns.
扔进水里
In the water.
溅起水花
Splash.
现在 都滚出去吧
Now, get the fuck out of here, man.
除了你 小子
Except you, young one.
你什么都没说?
You ain't say shit back there?
没说 他们自己泄了底 说我的指纹在其中一把枪上
oh, no. they fucked up when they told me my prints were on one of them guns, right?
我可是亲自把指纹擦掉的
And I wiped them shits down myself.
他们说是我的那把枪 还不是我的
And the one they said was mine wasn't even.
况且如果他们有我什么把柄
and If they would've had anything past my name,
他们早就把我扣留了 对吧
they would've kept me, right?
- 好吧 - 好的 String
- All right. - All right, String.
带上门
Lock that door.
你有断线钳吗
You got a bolt cutter?
我想要一把好使的
'Cause I'm gonna need a good one.
窗户那边有两把
Got two in the window there.
你把这个挂在鸭脖子上?
You hung this on a duck?
当然
Of course.
1200块
$1,200.
很公道
Fair enough.
- Nick - 好久不见 Mikey
- Nick. - It's been a while, Mikey.
对 确实
Yeah, it has.
不过你名字...
But your name has been...
最近出现在我脑海里
ringing out in my mind lately.
哦 是吗
oh, Yeah?
我合伙人打电话来
My man called.
说你要跟我提货
Said you was gonna take a re-up from me.
嗯 他们也是这么跟我说的
Yeah, that's what they told me, too.
Nicky Sobotka 干这营生
Nicky Sobotka, living the life.
谁想得到呢
Who fucking knew?
你想要多少
So how much you looking for?
一周两到三份G包
Two or three G-packs a week.
我过去从"希腊人"那儿进
I was getting that shit from the Greek's people.
- 每包四百 - 四百?
- Four each. - Four?
我批发价是五百 伙计
I wholesale for five, man.
这我就不知道了
I don't know.
他们说你没问题的 所以...
They told me you were gonna be straight with it. so...
Sergei
Sergei.
最近可好 伙计
What up, dawg?
我这有个你们的朋友 说用四百买一包
I got a friend of yours here says we're giving Gs at four.
是吗
Yeah?
好吧 去他的 是的 没关系
All right, fuck it. Yeah, it's fine.
还有件事
Another thing.
我想确定不是你们的人...
I wanna know it wasn't your people...
某晚把那尸体扔到Potee街 知道吗
dropped that body over on Potee Street the other night, you know?
我问是因为他有个希腊名字...
I'm asking 'cause it was someone with some Greek-ass name...
如果不是扔到了我的门口 我才不在乎呢
and fuck if he wasn't dumped in front of a house I was using.
他有手吗
Did he have hands?
他有脸吗
Did he have a face?
有吗
Yes?
那就不是我们的人
Then it wasn't us.
白痴
Idiot.
你有个高层的朋友 Nicky
You got friends in high places, Nicky.
- 给你四百一包 - 好 谢了
- Four a pack for you. - All right, cool.
多亏了俄国佬的手机
Thank God for the Russian's cell phone.
他们也许能换掉货仓的电话
They might be laying off the warehouse line,
但至少他不会换手机
but at least he ain't changing that up.
他有手吗 他有脸吗
Did he have hands? Did he have a face?
有吗 那就不是我们干的
Yes? Then it wasn't us.
什么玩意
What the fuck is that?
男用钱包
It's a man's purse.
你这种欧洲男士偶尔会带一个
European men like yourself sometimes carry one.
她们那些人不会就楞在那
Them people ain't right over there.
总得找个地方放麦克风
The kel-mike has to go somewhere.
况且 在我们得到想要的前
Besides, you might have hands all over you
你可能已经全身上下被摸遍了
before we get what we need.
确有可能
Indeed I might, luv.
我们什么时候冲进去由你决定
It'll be your call when we come through the doors.
你想让我们进去了 就说...
You want us in, you say...
什么来着
What was it?
"正是"(就是那儿)
"Spot on."
就是"对"的意思
It means "exactly."
记住 得让她们会先提及价格和性交易...
And remember, they have to bring up the money and the sex first...
然后暗示可以开始了
then an overt attempt to engage.
正是
Spot on.
Freamon警探 Baltimore凶杀科
Detective Freamon with Baltimore Homicide.
听着 你们暴力犯罪逮捕计划有没有...
Listen, what do you guys have in VICAP for male victims...
一个无头或无脸同时 失去双手的男性受害者
headless or faceless, and missing both hands?
可能是在东中部地区
Middle Atlantic region probably.
资本预算中的450万
$4.5 million in the capital budget
会获得参议院和众议院通过
that's set to pass House and Senate both.
钱会在明年结算期到账
Money'll be allocated for the fiscal period next year.
恭喜 Frank
Congratulations, Frank.
什么码头工人会喝香槟啊?
What kind of stevedore drinks champagne?
Nat 选举那事
So, Nat, about the election.
我只要再一年去争取到疏通运河
I just need one more year to bring the dredging home.
我就要这些
That's what I need.
轮到Ott了 Frank
Ott's turn, Frank.
Frank
这位是华盛顿来的FBI的Koutris探员
This is Agent Koutris of the FBI down in Washington.
他在那从事反恐工作
He's with the counterterrorism people down there.
- 反恐? - 他今晚要求我们协助
- Terrorism? - He needs our help tonight.
11-34 报告你的位置
11-34, what's your 20?
我在Wicomico街的立交桥上
I'm at the overpass on Wicomico.
收到
Copy that.
好的 车来了
Okay, we're on here.
晚上好
Good evening.
颜料干粉
Paint pigments.
为Fairfield的森马工厂运进来的
They ship them in for the SCL plant down at Fairfield.
在这里面某处
It's in there somewhere.
启动
Run it.
所有桶的密度都一样
Same consistencies on all the barrels.
里面确实没藏什么
Nothing else in there, really.
除了干粉什么都没有
Nothing but the pigments.
怎么了
What's going on?
我也不知道 "马面"
I don't know nothing, Horse.
我对天发誓
Swear to God.
今晚我只是个Locust码头的无语白人
Tonight, I'm just a dumb white boy from Locust Point.
你知道 我是带着尊敬说出这些话的 Brie
You know, I'm saying this out of respect, Brie.
我爱他如同兄弟
I love the man like he was my brother,
但遇到这类事...
but when it comes to something like this...
你说话比我说更有用
he gonna listen to you more than he listen to me.
你这么想?
You think so?
我跟他说我儿子的事 一点用都没有 现在有用吗
All I put in his ear about my son didn't do a damn thing, now, did it?
我一直告诉他多帮帮D'Angelo...
All them times I told him that he needed to do more for D'Angelo...
结果呢
and what happened?
他感受得到
He feel for that.
他对你有感情
He feel for you.
我相信他也没想到会这样
I know he didn't see it coming.
- 我们没人能想到 - 我能
- None of us seen it coming. - I did.
我发誓 我想到了
I swear, I saw it.
但他就是不肯听我的
He ain't listen to me then.
你凭什么认为他现在会听
Why the hell you think he gonna listen now?
因为我们的货很差...
'Cause we got a weak product...
却没有足够的打手维持地盘
and we holding on to prime real estate with no muscle.
Wee-Bey没了
I don't got Wee-Bey,
Stinkum Bird都没了
Stinkum, Bird.
听着 我知道你心情沉重
Now look, I know that your heart is heavy.
我知道
I know.
但现在人家已经杀到门口了
But them wolves is at that door.
只要那些高楼还没倒
As long as them Towers are still standing,
我就不会倒
I am, too.
如果让我们为之奋斗的一切付之东流
And I'll be damned if I'm gonna let everything we fought for
我会不得好死
go to shit.
所以我会跟他谈的
So I'll talk to him.
Cromwell先生
Mr. Cromwell.
决定啊决定
Decisions, decisions.
要两个会不会过分了
Would it be wrong to take two?
好小子
Attaboy.
我们该上楼了
We should get upstairs.
只有颜料干粉
Nothing but paint pigments.
相信我 老伙计 就在那
Trust me, old friend. It's there.
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch!
好了
Okay, then.
好
Right.
也许 我们能先聊聊?
Maybe, we could talk about this first?
我们...
we...
你们想什么时候都行
Any time you guys want.
钱易手了 对吧
The money changed hands, right?
听起来是这样
Sounded that way.
他们说了性交易了吗
And they talked about sex?
- 绝对的 - 你们想什么时候都行
- Definitely. - Any time you guys want.
等等
Hang on.
老天
Oh, God.
已经"真枪实弹"了吗?
Is it soup yet?
正啥的 正是!
Spot something. Spot on it.
行动
Let's go.
喔哦 拿这个干嘛
Whoa. Why?
我们要快速打开门冲进去
We're supposed to take the door and get in quick.
冷静点
Calm the fuck down.
她们又不会把半打妓女冲进马桶
It ain't like they gonna flush a half dozen whores down the toilet.
- 谁 - Baltimore警察
- Who is it? - Baltimore police.
你们想怎样
What do you want?
把你们关起来
To lock your ass up.
- 举手 - 让我看见 举手
- Hands. - Let me see them. hands.
- 后面还有两个 - 合作点 女士们
- Two more in the back. - Come on, ladies.
你们迟了
You're late.
他没事吧
He okay?
挂不了
He'll live.
"...估计有1125千克经待加工的可卡因..."
...estimated at 1, 125 kilograms of processed crack cocaine...
"价值超过4千5百万美元"
is estimated to be in excess of $45 million.
"联邦官员向第六新闻频道证实..."
Federal officials have confirmed to Channel 6 News...
"调查还将继续..."
that their investigation is ongoing...
"尚未逮捕任何人..."
and that while no arrests have yet been made...
"该次捕获行动沉重打击了一个据信与..."
the seizure itself has severely disrupted the operations of a group...
"哥伦比亚贩毒恐怖组织有关的团伙"
believed to have ties to Colombian narco-terrorist...
各位 这才是个案子
Now, that, gentlemen, is a case.
你们要能把那些罪名安在
God forbid you two should put something like that
我的朋友 Frank Sobotka头上...
on my friend, Frank Sobotka...
我死也瞑目了
I would die happy.
我们的案子有进展
Our case is progressing.
很好 你们能起诉什么
Great, what can you charge?
还没到那个份上
We're not at that point.
我们已经为窃听走私活动做好了准备
We've got wires into a smuggling operation
走私内容包括毒品和女人
that we've linked to both drugs and women.
而且很可能 他们就是两个月前...
And in all likelihood,that they're the people who were bringing in the girls...
走私那些死在集装箱里的女子的人
who turned up dead in that can two months ago.
现在我们监视着一个我们相信 是毒品转运点的地方
Now, we're on one location that we believe is a transshipment point for narcotics.
而昨晚 如果你们看了简报...
And last night, if you check the 24s...
你们会发现我们突击了一家涉案的妓院
you'll see that we hit a brothel we also think ties in.
再有一两个月的录音和电话记录...
A month or two more on the taps and DNRs...
我们就能揪出高层黑手
and we will be able to identify the top-end players.
你们突击了一家妓院?
You hit a brothel?
滨水区公寓 高档妓院
Waterfront condo, high-end.
上帝
Jesus.
好吧 如果你们发现
okay. If you find anything
固定客户之类的名单 毁了它
that looks like a list of steady customers, flush it.
那上面大概一半的名字都出现在
I mean, half the names in the Maryland Manual
马里兰指南上(州政府出版的政府指南)
are probably on it.
突击有遇到什么麻烦吗
Any problems on the raid?
一两个小问题吧 没什么解决不了的
A complication or two. Nothing we can't write around.
移民局扣押了那些女孩
Immigration is holding the girls.
而那个老鸨有合法居住权
And the madam, who has legal residency,
交了保释金就让她走了
we cut loose after she posted bail.
有试着审她们吗 看看有没有人会招
You try to interview them? See if any will roll?
在监听期间不会
Not while the taps are up.
最好让她们以为这只是此随机突击
Better to let them think it was a random raid
再看看今天能监听到什么
and see what's said on the wire today.
说正事
Cut to the chase.
我的谋杀案有进展吗
You any closer on my murders?
如果这些人就是走私女孩的人...
If these are the people who were importing those girls...
那么 我们就有进展了
then, yeah, we're closer.
知道越多 越有机会侦破这些案子
The more we learn, the more chance we have to clear those cases.
那么Frank Sobotka呢
What about Frank Sobotka?
我没听到你们提及他
I'm not hearing his name in here anywhere.
工会可能卷入了走私...
The union may be involved in the smuggling...
但我们认为应该仅此而已
but we're not getting a sense that it goes past that.
我们要查的是Frank Sobotka
This is about Frank Sobotka.
这案子现在大了
The case is bigger now.
听着 小妞 这是我的专案组
Look, missy, this is my detail.
我成立的
I started it.
现在我要问
Now, I'm asking,
你们能指控Frank Sobotka吗
do you have charges on Frank Sobotka?
这关头指控Sobotka 会让我们失去监听线...
Charging Sobotka at this point would lose us the wire...
和抓到真正目标的机会
and a chance at the real targets.
他就是真正目标
He is the real target.
耐心点 Stan
P-P-P-Patience, Stan.
- 我相信如果他们查下去... - 你欠我的 Erv
- I'm sure if they bring the case... - You owe me on this, Erv.
你要专案组
You asked for a detail,
我给了你专案组
I gave you a detail.
你要Daniels 我给了你Daniels
You asked for Daniels, I gave you Daniels.
好吧
Okay.
这么说...
so...
反正投票结束了...
Now the votes are in...
你把高尔夫奖杯搬到楼上的...
and you're moving your damn golf trophies upstairs
局长办公室了
to the commissioner's office...
就对我不理不睬了 是吧
now you're freezing me out, huh?
顶你们全家的肺
Fucking rat fuckers, all of you.
这是我的案子
This is my case.
我的
Mine!
而你们想来跟我说
And now you're gonna tell me
谁是目标?
who the target is?
不至于吧
Not fucking likely.
他说不行
He's saying no.
他说那些高楼都是我们打下来的...
He's saying we fought for every one of them Towers...
拱手送给他们 会让人以为我们好欺负
and to give them up now would mark us as weak.
他说如果我们这么做 "建议乔"就会骑到我们头上...
He's saying if we do this, Prop Joe would have it over us...
而我们会永世不得翻身
and we might never get out from under.
我们没货也没打手
We don't have the product or the muscle.
我跟他说了
I told him.
真的
I did.
他说他正尝试给我们找更好的货源
He say he still trying to find us a better connect.
至于打手...
And for muscle...
他说会给我们找到最好的
he's saying he sending us the best he can find.
"Mouzone大兄"
Brother Mouzone.
他让"大兄"来?
He sending in Brother?
从纽约过来
From New York.
到这做保护人
Coming down to work on retainer,
我们需要他留多久就多久
for as long as we need.
"Mouzone大兄"?
Brother Mouzone?
对
Yep.
"当时情况下 该警员无法拒绝..."
"At which point the officer was unable to resist...
"上述嫌疑人的服务..."
"the ministrations of the aforementioned suspect...
"不得不与对方发生性行为"
"and found himself brought to the point of a sexual act."
这事之后你会出名的 你知道吗
You're famous behind this, you know that?
这报告会让你成为警局传奇色狼
As a pervert, this report is gonna make you a BPD legend.
我不能作伪证啊 总得自圆其说吧
I can't perjure myself. I gotta explain it somehow.
混球 你违反了
Motherfucker, you have violated
半打的部门规章
a half dozen departmental regs right there.
更别提没有哪个公诉人
Not to mention that no state's attorney
会把这事在庭上宣传了
is gonna even bring this thing into court.
我们不会上法庭的 那些女孩都被驱逐了
We're not going to court. The girls are being deported.
我们的突击只是要惊动监听线 记得吗
We did the raid just to tickle the wire, remember?
她们有两个人 我处于劣势
There were two of them. I was outnumbered.
你玩我是吧
You fucking with me, right?
"Mouzone大兄"从纽约过来?
Brother Mouzone, from NYC?
我去找Avon 告诉他我没有足够打手
I went to Avon, told him I didn't have enough muscle
维持高楼区地盘 我这么说的
to hold down them Towers. Played it like that.
是啊 然后他就拉外援了
Yeah, and he reached out.
Joe 我仍然同意我们的交易
Joe, I'm still holding on to this deal.
知道我在说什么吗 只是有些事要处理
Know what I'm saying? This is just some shit we gotta deal with.
怎么处理
Deal with how?
兄弟 要是我能除掉他就自己动手了...
My nigger, I would take the motherfucker out if I could...
但不能让Avon知道是自己人干的 对吧
but Avon can't know it came from his own people, right?
你不会想让我派人去对付"大兄"吧
You don't think I'm gonna send any of my people up against Brother?
靠
Shit.
那黑鬼杀的人比中国坟墓里埋的还多
That nigger got more bodies on him than a Chinese cemetery.
那倒是
True.
听着 我只想说
Look, I'm just saying,
这是你的问题 不是我的
this your problem, not mine.
你想要我的货 就跟我交易
You want my product, you need to deal with it.
好吧 听着 我们还有时间
All right, so listen, we got some time here.
Avon得让人带话过去 带话回来...
Avon gotta send up word and wait for word to come back...
谈好价钱 跟"Mouzone大兄"商量 我是说 准备好整件事
set up a price, talk to Brother Mouzone, I mean, set up the whole shit.
这会花上一两周时间
And that's like a week or maybe two.
到时 你的人已经进入高楼了
And by that time, your people's gonna be in the Towers...
如果钱没问题 那该怎样就怎样
and if the money's right, then that is what it is.
一个纽约来的黑鬼改变不了既成事实
Ain't no nigger from New York gonna change the facts from the ground.
行吗
All right?
12-08呼叫11-37 你们在吗
12-08 to 11-37, you there?
11-37收到 有什么情况
11-37, what you got?
最近开来的那辆卡车要离开了
That last truck is on the move.
在这停了两天 什么都没卸
It sits there for two days and they don't offload a thing.
- 收到 - 他们在试我们
- 10-4. - They're testing us.
肯定转移的是合法的集装箱
They been moving clean cans.
- 垃圾没招来苍蝇 - 是吗
- The trash hasn't drawn any flies. - No?
我们刚取完最后一件 没问题
We just took out the last of it. No problems.
很好 我们可以开始了
Okay, then we go.
- llona怎样了 - 她在家 他们扣押了孩子们
- What about llona? - She is home. They kept the children.
孩子总会有的
There are always more children.
我们干嘛不录下那通电话
Why don't we tap that cell phone,
虽然不知道电话那头是谁
even if we don't know who we're tapping?
那通电话只是个成立依据
That call might just be our PC.
这个才是正主儿
And this here is the little king of everything.
老大 Boss Man
部门里有多少人
So how many we got in the sector?
两班轮班 外加联防队
Double shift, plus the Flex Squad,
缉毒队...
DEU...
还有机动部队派给我们的人
and a dozen guys Tactical sent us.
每个街角都有我们的人
We're on every corner.
今天真他妈安静
Pretty damn quiet today.
今天
Today.
走吧
Let's go.
纽约 WNY-82K5 帝国大厦
New York WNY-82K5 The Empire State
警官
Officer.